Jonas Schmidt

Professional Summary

Diligent problem-solver with resourceful approach to challenges and organized style. Leverages programming knowledge expertise to manage job functions. Excellent communicator with focus on results. Extremely goal-oriented and driven to find the simplest and most efficient solution to complex logical problems. Extremely curious and driven especially by a desire to learn

EXPERIENCE

University of Louisiana at Lafayette — Research Assistant

January 2023 - PRESENT

Emerging Computing Technology Lab

- Designed and developed hyperdimensional computing algorithms in Python to perform classification tasks
- Performed analysis on performance of different algorithms
 Invited to and attended a ULS-sponsored academic summit to present my research experience

January 2022 - December 2022

Virtual Reality Lab

- Utilized VR software and equipment to aid in designing applications for industry use
- Worked both independently in a fast-paced laboratory
 environment
 - Participated in research regarding the psychological effects of VR

University of Louisiana at Lafayette — Student Worker

January 2021 - December 2021

- Maintained accurate and up-to-date student records
- Coordinated the processing of transcripts, including verifying student information and communicating with other institutions if needed
- Provided excellent customer service to students, parents, and faculty, answering questions and resolving issues in a timely and professional manner

Art and Design (3D and 2D)

Experience with Adobe Photoshop and proficiency with Blender 3-D software. Four years of art classes taken in high school with two accolades to show for.

- (337) 330-6417
- New Orleans, LA 70122

Website, Portfolio, Profiles

- linkedin.com/in/jonas-schmidt-0259a7246
- github.com/Jonaschmidt

Skills

- · Analytical Thinking
- Teamwork and Collaboration
- Strong Adaptability
- GitHub
- · C++, Java, Python, MIPS
- Photoshop, Blender (Graphic Design)

Education

University of Louisiana at Lafayette –

Bachelors of Science in Computer Science and Mathematics, minor in Psychology

3.55 GPA

Expected Graduation: 5/2024

Benjamin Franklin High School

New Orleans, LA – Highschool Diploma

Graduation class of 2020

Graduated magna cum laude and with several AP credits

Awarded "Best in class" – AP Studio Art 2-D Awarded "Most Creative" – Honors Studio Art II